question_data = [
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"Luigi is taller than Mario?","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"Pac-Man was invented by the designer Toru Iwatani while he was eating pizza.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In the &quot;S.T.A.L.K.E.R.&quot; series, the Freedom faction wishes to destroy the supernatural area known as  &quot;the Zone&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In &quot;The Sims&quot; series, the most members in a household you can have is 8.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In Riot Games &quot;League of Legends&quot; the name of Halloween event is called &quot;The Reckoning&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In the video game &quot;Transistor&quot;, &quot;Red&quot; is the name of the main character.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In &quot;Call Of Duty: World At War&quot;, the first appearance of the &quot;PPSH-41&quot; in &quot;Zombies&quot; was in the map &quot;Der Riese&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"Donkey Kong was originally set to be a Popeye arcade game.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In &quot;Super Mario 64&quot;, collecting 100 coins on a level will give you a 1-UP.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"Each piece in Tetris is called a tetris.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"The game &quot;Jetpack Joyride&quot; was created by &quot;Redbrick Studios&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"The Paradox Interactive game &quot;Stellaris&quot; was released in 2016.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In the video game &quot;Splatoon&quot;, the playable characters were originally going to be rabbits instead of squids.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"TF2: The Medic will be credited for an assist if he heals a Spy that successfully saps a building.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"The ultimate phrase used by Pharah from Overwatch is: &quot;Justice rains from above!&quot;","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In &quot;Mario Kart 64&quot;, Waluigi is a playable character.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"&quot;Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater&quot; takes place on Shadow Moses Island.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"The Konami Code is known as Up, Up, Down, Down, Left, Right, Right, Left, B, A, Start.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"Watch_Dogs 2 is a prequel.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In the game &quot;Melty Blood Actress Again Current Code&quot;, you can enter Blood Heat mode in Half Moon style.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In the game &quot;Until Dawn&quot; Emily is the only playable character who can be killed by another playable character directly.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"The game Garry&#039;s Mod originally took assets and codes from the popular Half Life 2 mod JBmod.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"English new wave musician Gary Numan founded the video game development company Facepunch Studios in March 2009.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In &quot;Need for Speed: Porsche Unleashed&quot;, the player can only drive cars manufactured by Porsche.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"Niko Bellic is the protagonist of Grand Theft Auto IV.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}
]